(Penny:)I was wondering if you could
maybe teach me a little physics.
(Penny:)-A little physics?
-Yeah.
(Sheldon:)There's no such thing.
Physics encompasses the entire universe.
(Sheldon:)From quantum particles to supernovas.
(Sheldon:)From spinning electrons
to spinning galaxies.
(Penny:)Okay, cool,
I don't need the PBS special.
I wanna know enough
so I can talk to Leonard about his job.
(Penny:)Like Bernadette does.
(Sheldon:)-Why can't Leonard teach you?
-Because I wanna surprise him.
(Sheldon:)Can't you surprise him
in some other way?
(Sheldon:)For example, I'm sure he'd be delightfully
taken aback if you clean your apartment.
(Howard:)Come on, Sheldon,
this is important to me.
(Sheldon:)This would be
a massive undertaking...
(Sheldon:)...and my time
is both limited and valuable.
(Penny:)You're sitting here
playing video games all day.
(Sheldon:)Okay, point.
(Sheldon:)What sort of foundation do you have?
(Sheldon:)Did you take any science classes
in school?
(Penny:)Sure. I did the one with the frogs.